<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>da.wg</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on da.wg</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 11:40:29 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>cryptoZombies [solidity]</title>
      <link>/posts/cryptozombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 11:40:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cryptozombies/</guid>
      <description>CryptoZombies&amp;rsquo;s Website
 Note: I already have a little bit of programming experience so I will be relating some of the concepts to Javascript/C++ concepts. A great resource for learning Javascript is freeCodeCamp&amp;rsquo;s Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification course
 Lesson 1 Solidity&amp;rsquo;s code is encapsulated in contracts.
contract: fundamental building block of Ethereum applications - all variables and functions belong to a contract. Starting point of all your projects</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DeFi</title>
      <link>/posts/defi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 20:34:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/defi/</guid>
      <description>Sources: Finematics
Note: I&amp;rsquo;m already familiar with the basics of DeFi (eg. what it is, key projects, Uniswap, MetaMask) so there won&amp;rsquo;t be any notes after those things. If you wish to start at the beginning, the finematics article is a great start
View my project specific posts:
Lending and Borrowing: One of the most important aspects of any financial system
money market: area of traditional finance that specializes in short term lending and borrowing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CryptoCred&#39;s TA Series</title>
      <link>/posts/cryptocred/cryptocred/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 20:50:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cryptocred/cryptocred/</guid>
      <description>Link to original videos
 #1: Candlestick Charts What is technical analysis:  way to make probabilistic forecasts of future price behaviour  you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be a technical trader, you can use it to look for best risk/reward long entries if you&amp;rsquo;re fundamentally bullish on an asset   can be thought of as a risk management tool  Candlestick Anatomy:  red = closing price below opening price green = closing price above opening price OHLC = Open, High, Low, Close  Side note: lines drawn on a particular time frame are still displayed at different time frames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blog init</title>
      <link>/posts/blog-init/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 21:10:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog-init/</guid>
      <description>Hey there and welcome to my blog! This blog will help document my journey into crypto and trading. Since discovering Bitcoin and crypto 9 months ago, I&amp;rsquo;ve spent all of my free time away from school work researching about everything in the space. I now feel like I have a good understanding of:
 the history and major dates of crypto names and what they do of majority of the Top 100 coins major areas of innovation (eg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/archive/</guid>
      <description>archives</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/search/</guid>
      <description>search</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
